Preliminary Guide to the John A. Wilson papers, 1974-1993 MS2190
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1974-1993; Series 3
  - International Cultural and Trade Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - International Cultural and Trade Center - resources, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - International Village Southwest, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - International Village Southwest, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Interstate Compact - Placement of Children, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Interstate compact on juveniles, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Iris Lewis fundraiser, 1982; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Issue sheets, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - J.B. Johnson Nursing Home, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Jack Evans Jr. Resolution, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Jackson Edward, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Jacques Chavalier, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - James Apartments, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - James Apartments - 1425 N Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - JAWs newsclippings, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Jay Hellman, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - JCC, 1989; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Jefferson Hotel, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Jefferson House, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Jefferson Junior High School: A Local Solution to a National Problem", undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 9)
  - Jerry Washington, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Jewish Community Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Community Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Community Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Community Center - surplus property, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Jewish National Fund, 1991 April 28; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Johns Hopkins PUD, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Johns Hopkins PUD 11, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Jones Paul E, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Joseph Danzansky Memorial, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Tancos, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Julius Hobson Plaza condiminium, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Kahn alley closing, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Kahn alley closing, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Kaiser Permanente, undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kathleen A.H. Graff, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Kennedy Center, 1990; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy-King Dinner, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Kevin Hein, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Kutzera, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - L Street Coop Assoc/919 L Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Land Acquisition Housing Development Opportunity (LAHDO), undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Larry Brockman, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Larouche for President, 1992; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 11)
  - Lauer Lalley and Associates Research, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lauer Lalley and Associates Research, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Law Enforcement Emergency, undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lawsuits and class actions against JAW, undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Liberty Train, 1987; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - License plates, undated; Series 3 (Box 86, Item 1)
  - Life Imprisonment Minimum Sentence Act S-182, undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - List of Petition signers, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Literature - Mayoral campaign, 1982; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Littter Control Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Logan Circle area shelters, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Logan Circle Citizen Association - Historic district application, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Logan Circle Community Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Logan Circle Project - Rehab, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Logan Inn, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Logan Shops - 1100 Rhode Island Ave NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lucia Rapley - Aging Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Luis Zapata, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer Report, 1991 August 28; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 4)
  - Malpractice insurance public hearing, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Marchetta, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Market House Audit, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mary Healey, 1982 April 26; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Mary Healy, undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Materials for prostitution legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Mayor Barry's Youth Leadership Institute Mentorship Program, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Mayor's Orders, 1988; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mazique Parent Child Center - Resolution, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Mazique Parent Child Center [1/2], undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mazique Parent Child Center [2/2], undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Media - Campaign, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Media campaign - Rothstein and Buckley, 1980; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Medical Malpractice Litigation Summary, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Medicare Supplement Insurance, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Medlantic Healthcare Group, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mega Foods Inc., undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Memorials, undated; Series 3 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health Care - Dixon File, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Mental Health Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Mental Health Plan - Final, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Mental Health Plan - Final, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Mental Health System Implementation Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - MET Grant, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - MET- Grant, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Metnal Health - Preliminary System Implementation Plan, 1986; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Metnal Health Reorganization Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Metro - SW reduction in bus service, 1980; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Metro - Waterside Station, 1983; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Metro Bus Garage - Southeastern, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Metro contracts, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Metro Mi2, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Metro mid-city Greenline, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Metro Navy Yard Station, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Metro route, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Metro Waterfront Station, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Miami Nice" Presentation/Graduation, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 6)
  - Miner Teacher College Building/Howard University, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Minority contracting, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Minority contracting, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Minority contracting, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Misc, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Misc records, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Misc. tributes and speeches, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - MLK Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Morton Bender, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Motion Picture Center - Foggy Bottom, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Motorcade, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Mount Vernon Plaza Hodag Proposal, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mount Vernon Project, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. Ana Springer, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Ms. Sherner, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Multi-family purchase, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Nathanson Pricing Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - National Learning Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - National Wildlife Federation PUD 83-17C, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - NE Helliport, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Near North Citizens Against Crime and Drugs, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood municipal offstreet parking, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Neighborhood planning councils, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - New Georgetown Proposal, undated; Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - News Channel 8, 1992 December 29; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 7)
  - Newsletter, 06/1990; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper and magazine articles, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper articles, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper articles - hate crimes, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper material, undated; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 12)
  - Nighclub zone, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - No-fault correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Noise Control Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Noise Control Act, 1977; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Nominating petitions, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Nominating petitions, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Notes - Linkage, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Nurse Practices Act - Bill 5-50, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nursing shortage, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NW Urban Renewal #1, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - O Street Community Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Oath of Office, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Occupational Therapist, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - OCF Reports, undated; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 1)
  - Old Drafts, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Old receipts, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Old vouchers, undated; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 10)
  - Omnibus narcotics bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Other Side of Victory/Story of a People: A Dream Deferred, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 3)
  - Our Town, 1991 March 20; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 23)
  - Outdoor Cafe - 1310 New Hampshire Ave NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 75)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 76)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 77)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 78)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 79)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 80)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 81)
  - Oversize posters, undated; Series 3 (Box 82)
  - Palm Cafe (Logan Inn) 1338 R Street, undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Paradise Cafe, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Parcel 11 (Shaw), undated; Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Parcel 14 (Capital Station NE), undated; Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Parcel 18, undated; Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Parcel 19 (Shaw Urban Renewal), undated; Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Parcel 23 - Shaw Urban Renewal Areas, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Parcel 7 (H Street NE), undated; Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Parcel 76, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Parcels 19 and 22 - United House of Prayer, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Parole revocation, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Parole Revocation Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Pastor Harvey Lewis, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Pay Schedule - Expected Service, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - PCP and DC General Hospital Program, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Peabody's Mass Ave Court, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania Ave Development Corp, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Pepco, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Pepco [1/2], undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Pepco [2/2], undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Pepco Rate Increase, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Perry School Site NW1, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Pet Shop - HS Hearing Horse Drawn Carriages, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Petition for Residential Permit Parking, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Phillips Collection, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Phillips Collection Alley Closing, 1987; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Phone book instructions, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Photocopies of plaques, undated; Series 3 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 3 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1960s and undated; Series 3 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Some of these images (the ones not part of the photograph album) were added in 2018 and was part of the donation from Bonnie Wilson, December 7, 2018 (accession 2018.050)
  - Photo project, 1980 May; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Photos color transparencies (in blue Folders and white boxes), undated; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Photos negatives, undated; Series 3 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Pictures, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Pitts Contract, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Plate from the Embassy of Saudi Arabia, Series 3 (Box 83, Item 2)
  - Plate from University of Maryland Eastern Shore's Presidents' Club, 1987; Series 3 (Box 83, Item 3)
  - Plate from the Foggy Bottom Community, 1987; Series 3 (Box 83, Item 4)
  - Plate from 4H, Series 3 (Box 83, Item 5)
  - Police and Correctional Officers Representation, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Police Department, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Poll coverage, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Population and housing data, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Population stats, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Postering, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Postering and leafletting, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Potomac Boat Club, 1988-1990; Series 3 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Potomac Riverfest, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Poverty in DC, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - PR 6-442 Banking superintendent, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Precinct 83 Walk, 1988 September 10; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Pregnancy and Leave Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Pregnancy Anti Discrimination Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Prescription Drug Information, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Presidential primary, 1992 May; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Press, undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Press clips, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1975-1977; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Prison controversy, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Prison information, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Prisoner Screening Project, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Procurement, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Procurement - Committee on Government Operations, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Procurement Practices Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Productivity Report - Mayor's, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Programs, 1975-1992; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Progress Report on Comprehensive Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Prohibition of Discrimination in the Provision of Insurance Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Prostitution, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Prostitution - Logan Circle, 1985-1986; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Prostitution Enforcement Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Prostitution Enforcement Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Public Defender Service, 1982-1983; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Public Hall Regulation Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Public Housing, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Public Housing - Mayor's Report, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Public Housing Department Reorganization Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Public Housing Emergency Council, 1988; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Public Housing Regulations, 1987; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Public Housing Report, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Public Utilities Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - PUD Linkage Plans, 1987; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Questionnaires, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Quoton Margueritte, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - R. Kling's Project, undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Radio and brochure, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Randall School - Robert Ball, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Rape crisis center, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Reading file, 1987 Janury; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Reading file, 1987 February; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Reading file, 1987 March; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Reading file, 1987 April; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Reading file, 1987 May; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Reading file, 1987 June; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Reading file, 1987 July; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Reading file, 1987 August; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Reading file, 1987 September; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Reading file, 1987 October; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Reading file, 1987 November; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Reading file, 1987 December; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Reading file, 1988 January; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Reading file, 1988 January; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Reading file, 1988 March; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Reading file, 1988 April; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Reading file, 1988 May; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Reading file, 1988 June; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Reading file, 1988 July; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reading file, 1988 August; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reading file, 1988 September; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Reading file, 1988 October; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Reading file, 1988 November; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Reading file, 1988 December; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Reading file, 1982 December; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Reading file, 1983 January; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Reading file, 1983 January; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Reading file, 1983 April; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Reading file, 1983 April; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Real Property Credit Line Deed of Trust Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Recall, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Receipts, undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Recommendation, 1989; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations, 1975; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Recommendations, 1987; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Recommendations, 1989; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Recommendations, 1985; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Recommendations, 1982; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Recommendations, 1986; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Recommendations, 1981; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Recommendations, 1983; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Recommendations, 1980; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Recommendations, 1990; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations, undated; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations, 1979; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Recycling legislation and information, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Redistricting, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Redistricting, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Redistricting, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Reginald Robinson, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Registration instructions, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Related Materials - Linkage, 1988; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Renal dialysis, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Renovations of District Bldg and Williamson Apts, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Rent Control, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rent Control, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rent control, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Rent control, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Rent control, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Rent control, 1980; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Rent control, 1985; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Rent Control - Heating and Oil, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Rent control and conversion information, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Rent Control Bill 3-321, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Rent control issues, 1988; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Rent control referendum, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Rent control regulations, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Rent control studies, 1987; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Rent Stabilization Exemption Act, 1979; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Rental Housing Act, 1984; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Rental Housing Act/Residential Loan Exemption Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Rental Housing Conversion Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Rental Housing Conversion and Sale Act, 1980; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Rental Housing Conversion and Sale Act Amendments, 1981; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Rental Housing Conversion Regulation Act, 1980; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Rental Housing conversion sale, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Republicans for Wilson, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Requests for souvenirs, undated; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Residency Preference Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Residential Parking business, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Resolutions, 1986; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Resolutions, 1986; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions, 1990; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1980; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1981; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1982; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1983; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1984; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1979; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1987; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions - Ceremonial, 1977-1978; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions for the Future, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Restaurant and Liquor Dealers, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Results - Primary - Ward 2, 1982 September 14; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Results - primary election, 1984 September 11; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Rev. Douglas Moore, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Revenue Requests, 1980; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Reverand John J. Koger Resolution, undated; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Review of unsolicited offer to develop parcel 57-2, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Revitalization Plan Howard Gateway Shaw, undated; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Re-zoning DuPont circle, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Rhode Island Ave NW Hotel Emergency Shelters, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Rippeteau Darrel D, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Riverside Associates/Capitol Point Project, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Robin Vasquez - child support, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rolodex of business cards [1 of 3], Series 3 (Box 84, Item 1)
  - Rolodex of business cards [2 of 3], Series 3 (Box 84, Item 2)